出来
Get out.
黎巴嫩乡村地区   贝鲁特北部 20公里
检查屋子后门
Check the back of the house.
艾斯特
Ester!
你快走
我不能扔下你不管
你是你爸爸的骨肉
他们要抓的是你
快走
放开我  快放开我
Get off me! Let me go! Get off!
你爸在哪
Where's your father?
敢吐我一脸?
Spit in my face?
他在哪
Where is he?!
把她扔进车里
Put her in the car.
放开  放开我
Let go! Let me go! Get off me!
好了索菲亚  咱们该聊聊了
OK, Sofia, it's time to talk.
贝鲁特市区
我女儿被莱瑟比抓走了
Leatherby has my daughter.
艾斯特在他手上
He has Ester.
你去了我家  做了承诺
You stood in my home. You made a promise.
没错
Yeah.
我需要你帮忙
Well, I need your help.
帮我把她救出来
You get her out for me.
不管你们对我有没有成见
Whatever you think of me,
艾斯特是我仅剩的希望
Ester is the one true thing I have left,
可我却没能保护她
and I wasn't there for her.
卡马里  我们说了会帮你
Kamali, we said we had your back,
我们是认真的
and we meant it.
这事交给我们
Now you need to let us do that.
你要活着才有价值
You are no use to us dead.
李奥  我们保证会带她回来的
Leo, I swear to you that we'll bring her home.
就这样
Ok.
上校  我们去把她女儿救回来
Colonel, we're gonna go get his daughter back.
我需要你也做点事
Then I'll need something from you.
悉听尊便
Anything.
你比任何人都了解这里
You know this place better than anyone else.
索菲亚·阿布德是唯一的线索
Sofia Abboud is the only lead we have,
是弄清朱海瑞计划的仅有机会
our only chance to find out what Al-Zuhari is planning.
把道尔顿找出来
Find me Dalton.
你爸爱你吗  索菲亚
Does your father love you, Sofia?
当然
Of course.
你知道他一直在资助朱海瑞
You know he's been giving financial aid to Al-Zuhari,
你也清楚
and you know about
朱海瑞去年在约旦的暴行
the atrocity Al-Zuhari staged in Jordan last year.
我对政治不感兴趣
Politics does not interest me.
那次在约旦被袭的受害者
The victims of that Jordan attack--
其中不光有美国军人
they weren't just U.S. Military personnel--
还有妇女儿童
they were women and children,
以及穆斯林
Muslims, too.
你们的子民  索菲亚
They're your people, Sofia.
你父亲让你给朱海瑞捎信了  对吗
Your father gave you a message to give to al-Zuhari, didn't he?
你为什么要带我来这
Why have you brought me here?
他是在利用你  操纵你
He's using you, manipulating you.
这不是爱
That's not love.
你只是个棋子
You're a pawn.
那你呢  你算什么
And you? What are you?
你还算女人吗
Are you even a woman?
有丈夫  孩子或亲人吗
You have a husband, children, anyone?
你算什么东西
Who are you?
竟跟我聊爱情  有人爱你吗
You talk to me about love, but who loves you?
你有爱的人吗
Who do you love?
够了
Enough!
很简单
It's simple.
找到道尔顿之后联系我
You find Dalton, you call me,
我们负责把她带回来
we bring her in.
李奥  不用担心艾斯特
Leo, don't worry about Ester.
你信上帝吗
Do you believe in God?
如果信  那你该祈祷
Because if you do, you should pray
祈祷你父亲能够快点醒悟
that your father very quickly comes to understand
接受背叛的代价
and accept the cost of betrayal.
生活向来不公平  对吧
Life's not fair, is it?
总有人当炮灰
Someone always gets left behind.
曾经是我
Once upon a time it was me,
而这回...
and this time...
是你
it's you.
你可怜她了  对吗
You feel sorry for her, don't you?
所以我把你留在身边
That's why I keep you around--
提醒自己  以前的我会怎么想
to remind me of how I used to feel.
我们把卡马里的女儿还给他
So we let Kamali have his daughter back,
让他把钻石给我们
and he gives us the diamonds.
卡马里跟我玩心眼  我饶不了他
Kamali fucked with me. He's mine.
你...
You...
去帮我多找些人手
you find me some other man.
好
Ok.
知道了
英国佬总倒不尽的秘密  对吧
Every Englishman has his castle, huh?
字面意：每个英国人都有自己的城堡
可他是苏格兰人
Yeah, but he's Scottish.
有区别吗
There's a difference?
当然  苏格兰人生性好战  喜欢油炸巧克力棒
Yeah. The Scots like to fight and eat deep-fried Mars Bars,
而英格兰人从不会犯错
and the English are never wrong about anything.
他的营地位于此处往东18公里处
His compound is 18 clicks east of here.
安保情况呢
Security?
多达20个  持枪保镖
Up to 20 hired guns.
这家伙的安保工作做得够彻底啊
The guy doesn't do subtle, huh?
怎么了迈克  在想道尔顿的事吗
What is it, Mikey? You thinking about Dalton?
差不多吧
Yeah, a bit.
要我说  这事儿听洛克的没错
Yeah, in my eyes, dude, Locke made the right choice.
这是她自找的  疯婆娘
She had it coming. She's a fucking psycho.
但问题是  怎么没早点意识到呢
The problem I'm having is that nobody recognized it
不然也不至于弄成这样
till it was too late, man.
我们意识到了又能怎样
Well, we did, but what can we do, you know?
不是说我们
No, not us.
是说上级领导
The suits at the top.
他们总是无事生非 不是吗
They always want their pound of flesh, don't they?
重申一遍  瑞姆和金
Just to make sure, Richmond, Kim. Hmm?
你们去房顶做好狙击准备
You're taking sniper positions on the roof.
我和斯科特救出艾斯特后回集合点
Scott and I are gonna grab Ester and head for the exfil.
一旦谁有机会抓住莱瑟比
If anyone has a chance to grab Leatherby,
我们就逼他交代那女人的情报
we use him to get intel on the Abboud woman.
-收到  -明白
- Copy that. - Roger that.
手怎么样了
How's the hand?
疼
It hurts.
对不起
I'm sorry.
算了  这种事时有发生
These things happen.
我他妈都说对不起了
I said I'm fucking sorry, didn't I?
谢谢你
Thank you.
谢谢你把我从车里拉出来
Thank you for pulling me from the car.
真心感谢
Thank you.
有时候  我真希望你他妈能有点脾气
You know, sometimes I wish you had the guts to fucking hate me.
那女孩儿在哪儿
Where's the girl?
他说什么
What did he say?
我觉得他说的是"不会英语"
I think he said "No English."
不识相是吧
See that?
那女孩儿呢
Where's the girl?
我带你去
I'll take you there.
这还差不多
Thought so.
伙计  你可以考虑当外教了
You should consider teaching English as a second language, mate.
我现在就是啊
I am.
艾斯特  过来
Ester, come here.
来  把这个穿上
All right, put this on you.
快  有点汗
Hurry. It's a little bit sweaty.
套进去
Slip into that.
抱歉  码子大了
Sorry, it's a bit big.
没小孩儿的号
It's not made for kids.
都是给美国二胖穿的
Usually fat Americans.
接到目标
Target acquired.
迈克  稍等
Two seconds, Mike.
B1  B2正向集合点撤退
Bravo one and two headed for exfil now.
迈克
Mike.
发现莱瑟比
I have Leatherby.
重复  发现莱瑟比
Repeat, I have Leatherby.
妈的  把他带上
Fuck. Let's take him with us.
我这就过来
I'm coming to you.
收到
Roger.
Copy that.
在你10点方向
On your 10.
我过来了
Coming to you.
撤  快
Go. Move, move.
跟上
Come with me.
在那边  那边
Over there. Over there!
迈克
Mike!
安装完毕
Set.
快他妈上车  一群蠢货
Get in the fucking car, you fucking idiot!
贝鲁特东部  真主党营地
你好
Hello.
指挥官  我需要帮助
Commander, I need a favor.
好
Of course.
没问题
行  行
Ok. Ok.
第一次上战场是吧
First firefight, huh?
牛逼啊  小家伙
You kicked ass, kid.
干得不错
Well done.
谢谢
Thank you.
真心感谢你们每一位
All of you, thank you very much, though.
瞧你说的  他都不好意思了
Now look what you did. You made him blush.
放屁  我是说扯淡
Fuck off--I mean, knock it off.
我说的是"扯淡"
Knock it off, I said.
让你见笑了  斯科特中士
Excuse him. You'll find that Sergeant Scott
词汇量比较有限
has a very limited vocabulary.
总部  这里是B1
Zero, this is Bravo One.
目标已带回
We have the primary package,
但莱瑟比已开始行动  完毕
but Leatherby is very much in play. Over.
总部收到  B1
Zero. Roger, Bravo One.
卡马里那边有道尔顿少校的消息了吗
Anything from Kamali on Major Dalton?
长官  还没有
No word from Kamali yet, sir.
你疯了
You're crazy!
我说了  我什么都不知道
I told you I don't know anything!
你要干什么
What are you doing?
索菲亚  到底是什么消息
What's the message, Sofia?
不说?
No?
根本  根本就没消息
There is-- there is no message.
没消息
There is no message.
没消息是吧
No message?
最后一次机会  索菲亚
Last chance, Sofia.
哦  不
Oh, no...
不要
No.
看来我们进了真主党的地盘
It looks like we're in Hezbollah territory.
不是吧
No kidding.
有人把彩旗挂出来了
Someone hung the bunting out.
搞得跟啦啦队似的
It's a welcoming committee.
该死的  路障
Shit. Roadblock.
-该死  -小心  我们有伴了
- Shit. - Heads up. We've got company.
正从左翼上来
Coming at us on the left.
是的  他们是真主党的人  没错
Yeah, they're Hezbollah, all right.
操
Fuck!
艾斯特  你到后面去行吗
Ester, will you get in the back for me, please?
左边全是
We've got them on our left.
后面也有
Right behind us.
估计他们是莱瑟比的朋友
Guessing they're friends of Leatherby's.
六点方向
On our 6.
九点方向更多
And more on our 9.
投弹手堵住了六点位置
Bomber blocking our 6.
去那个小屋
Head for the hut.
收到
Copy that.
上  上  上
Go, go, go!
跑  快跑
Run, run!
快跑
Run!
关起来
Close it up!
你没事吧
You all right?
没事
Yeah.
总部  这里是B组
Zero, this is Bravo team.
是的  我们遇到了真主党的路障
Yeah, we ran into a Hezbollah roadblock
还丢了我们的车
and lost our ride.
这里是总部  收到
Zero. Roger.
看来真主党干扰了我们的视频信号
It looks like Hezbollah is jamming our visuals,
无信号
但我们会继续监监听他们的通讯
but we'll continue to monitor their comms.
保持通讯顺畅
Keep comms open at all times.
该死
Shit.
是莱瑟比
There's Leatherby.
快  赶紧离开这儿
Come on, let's get out of here.
一起去找个出口
Let's find an exit.
亲爱的  跟着我好吗
Honey, can you come with me?
好的  出发
Yeah. Move.
我们走
Let's go.
女士们  你们留下  我们马上回来
Ladies, you stay here. We'll be right back.
收到
Copy that.
如果他们是英国特种兵
If this is British Special Forces,
他们会监听真主党的通讯
they'll be monitoring Hezbollah comms.
给我把频道找出来
Find me the channel.
不  不  不要  不要
No. No! No! No!
是什么消息  索菲亚
What's the message, Sofia?
根本没有消息
There is no message.
没有?
No?
那只能这样了
This is how it's gonna be.
不要
No!
为什么  索菲亚
Why, Sofia,
你为什么要为朱海瑞保守秘密
would you do this for Al-Zuhari?
招了吧
Please.
不
No!
因为我爱他
你们说朱海瑞是禽兽
You say that it's al-Zuhari that is a monster,
侩子手
a butcher,
狂热分子
a fanatic.
但是你们一点也不了解他的为人
But you know nothing about him.
那你说说看
So why don't you tell me?
朱海瑞非常善良
Al-Zuhari is kind,
慷慨  还很温柔
generous, and gentle.
你到底是什么人
Who are you?
我是朱海瑞的妻子
I'm Al-Zuhari's wife.
他就在这  是吧
He's here, isn't he?
他带你来这和他见面
He brought you to meet him.
杀了我吧
Kill me.
我永远都不会说的
I will never tell you.
卡马里
Kamali.
你在贝鲁特待了三个月
You've been in Beirut for 3 months.
我对你的一举一动了如指掌
I've known your every move.
这里是我的地盘
This is my world.
洛克派我来的
Locke sent me.
那个女人呢
Where is the woman?
她就在这儿
She's here.
我想要帮你
I want to help you.
你?
You?
能帮我?
Can help me?
我们的目标一致
We both want the same thing.
到底是什么  说具体点
And what is that, exactly?
为了找到朱海瑞
To find Al-Zuhari.
为了阻止他
To stop him.
她是他的妻子
She's his wife.
那她就是关键  你说的没错
Then she is the key. You were right.
瑞秋  无论如何
Rachel, for what it's worth,
让我和她谈谈
let me speak to her.
枪
Gun.
手机
Phone.
可以了吗
Can I?
请便
Be my guest.
这是索菲亚·阿布德的档案  长官
The Sofia Abboud file, sir.
你从赫里福德远道而来
You're a long way from Hereford.
把我切到那个频道上
Get me voice on that channel.
是
Sir.
莱瑟比
Leatherby?
你是谁
Who is this?
我是菲利普·洛克
This is Philip Locke.
就是那位我常常听说的菲利普·洛克吗
The Philip Locke I've heard so much about?
我一直都觉得你是个
I always thought you were
被过度神话的死侏儒
an overrated little fucking dwarf, myself.
有可能  但我起码没有被
Possibly, but I wasn't the one
萨达姆的半吊子民兵俘虏  不是吗
capture by Saddam's weekend warriors, was I?
放我的人走  詹姆士
Let my boys go, James.
他们只是公事公办
They're just out there doing their job.
我保证
You have my word--
完事之后  我会挖出他们的心脏
when I'm done, I will carve out their hearts
寄回去给你  以示警醒
and send them back marked for your attention.
你的人撑不久的  菲尔
These boys won't beat the clock, Phil.
你别指望了
Don't count on it.
个人档案
一级机密
姓名: 索菲亚·阿布德
以下为索菲亚·阿布德曾到访之中东国家
天呐
Oh, my God.
我们去房顶
We're gonna head for the roof
从那儿找出口  行吗
and look for an exit there, yeah?
-走吧  -跟上
- Let's do it. - Let's move.
跟上
Yeah, moving.
我负责左边
I'll have a peek left, yeah?
好的  准备好了吗
Right. You ready?
上
Go, go, go, go.
艾斯特  待这别动
Ester, stand there.
快
Come on.
孩子  我让你待在那别动
I said stay over there, kid.
我爸爸是什么间谍吗
Is my dad some kind of spy?
蹲下
Get down.
这个问题你应该问他自己
That's the kind of question you should ask him.
你有亲人吗
Do you have a family?
我有几位父母  住在不同的州
Yeah. I got some parents, live in separate states,
这对我家来说是件好事
which is great for the family.
还有两三个兄弟
I got a couple of brothers.
统统是蠢货
They're idiots.
我问的是你自己的家庭
No, I meant of your own.
孩子  你问题太多了
You ask a lot of questions, huh, kid?
有烟吗
You got a cigarette?
今天没去商店
Didn't get to the shop today.
总部呼叫
Zero, over.
这里是B1
Yeah. This is Bravo One. Come in.
报告方位
What's your position?
前有埋伏  后有追兵
Right now we're stuck between a rock and a hard Scot.
看来真主党已经封锁了大黑
It looks like Hezbollah has locked down the whole of Dahieh.
想尽一切办法
You know if there was anything we could do...
明白
Yeah. I understand.
注意安全  对索菲亚·阿布德有新发现
Be advised, new intel on Sophia Abboud.
她是朱海瑞的妻子
She's al-Zuhari's wife.
该死
Shit.
你开玩笑吗
Are you fucking kidding me?
有道尔顿的消息吗
Do you have a location on Dalton yet?
没有
That's a negative.
如果阿布德招供了
If she's broken Abboud, she'll be headed
她肯定会去那女人要去的地方
for wherever that woman was going to be taken.
而且
And...
莱瑟比是唯一
Yeah. And Leatherby's the only other person
知道地点的人
who knows where that's at.
没错
That's a roger.
B1  去找莱瑟比要地址吧  行动
And, Bravo One, let's get that address from Leatherby. Out.
去屋顶
Up on the roof.
还等什么
What are we waiting for?
去杀了那些混帐东西
Let's kill those bastards, huh?
小子们  一切都该结束了
All right, boys. This is where it ends.
我们痛失希望与荣光
We have done with Hope and Honor.
迈克
Mike!
没事吧  艾斯特  跟着我
You all right? Ester, come with me.
我们沉湎爱与真相
We are lost to Love and Truth.
-该死  -怎么回事
- Fuck! - What is it?
上帝之怜悯...
God have mercy...
你没事吧
You're OK. You're OK.
...降临于我们
On such as we.
该死
Fuck.
艾斯特  艾斯特
Ester! Ester!
快点  我们走
Come on. Let's go.
别抬头
Keep down.
我是不会丢下我的士兵不管的
I am not leaving my lads out there.
行动
Let's move.
是  长官
Yes, sir.
走
Go!
斯科特  跟上
Scott! On me.
过来  过来
Come here! Come here!
快走
Move, move, move!
换弹匣
Changing! Changing!
阿迈
Mikey!
来了
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
谢了
Thanks.
不客气
De nada.
走
Move.
好
Ok.
上面有人开枪  蹲下
Gun overhead. Get down.
别杀他
Don't shoot him. Don't shoot him.
他是莱瑟比的男朋友
That's Leatherby's boyfriend.
我最好上去活捉他
I'd better go up there, take him alive,
逼他情夫告诉我们那女人要去哪
force his sugar daddy to tell us where he took the woman.
收到
Yeah, roger that.
艾斯特
Ester,
跟她们待在一起
stay with the girls, all right?
好
Yeah.
要乖哦
Behave for them, all right?
我们走
Moving.
这是总部  B1  我们正往那儿赶
This is Zero. Bravo One, we're on our way.
举起手来  过来
Hands up. Come here. Come here.
好  好  我可以帮你们
It's OK. It's OK. I-- It's OK. I can help you.
我可以帮忙
I can help you.
喂  "勇敢的心"
Oi, Braveheart!
停火
我们得谈谈  这是你的人吗
We need to talk. Does this belong to you? Huh?
给我十分钟
Give me 10 minutes.
明白
Gotcha.
好吧
All right.
索菲亚  你要把你知道的情况
Sofia, you have to tell this woman
告诉这位女士
what you know!
镇定点
我是你丈夫的朋友
他是这么称呼你的
你是我的眼
你是要和朱海瑞会面吗
Were you to meet Al-Zuhari?
我会放你离开
你开我的车走
嘘
Shh.
我让你自己考虑考虑
I'll leave you to think about it.
你和她说了什么
What did you say to her?
我说会放她离开这里
That I'd let her get out of here.
她绝对不会告诉我们朱海瑞在哪
She'll never tell us where Al-Zuhari is,
但是如果我们放她走的话
but if we let her escape,
她可以带我们去找他
she will lead us to him.
你们想要什么
What do you want?
想搭便车回家?
A free ride home, hmm?
即便我坐视不管
Even if I walk away,
真主党还是会置你们于死地
Hezbollah will still want you dead.
我们只想从你那得到地址  就这么简单
We just need an address from you. That's it.
你之前想把索菲亚·阿布德带到哪去
Where were you taking Sofia Abboud?
你们以为我会在乎他死活吗
Ha. You think I give a shit about him?
但是你上来了  不是吗
You're here, aren't you?
你为什么来这
Why are you here?
为了女王和国家吗
For Queen and Country, huh?
事实上  你来这里的原因和我是一样的
The truth is, you're here for the same reason I am--
我们肮脏的小秘密
our dirty little secret.
有意思极了吧  对吧
This is great fucking fun, eh?
你敢不敢在超市里排队时
Eh? Try telling that to the old dear standing next to you
告诉站在你旁边的老情人
in the queue in the supermarket.
杀人的那一刻你感到
You never feel more fucking ALIVE than the moment
前所未有的畅快淋漓
that you're killing another human being.
你那是说自己呢
You speak for yourself.
拜托  你是个聪明人
Oh, come on. Come on. You're a smart lad.
你知道你来这里是为了石油
You know you're out here
金钱和股息而滥杀无辜
killing for oil, dollars, and dividends.
只是这样伪装自己的真实意图比较简单
It's just easier to pretend otherwise.
当你在像这样的鬼地方
And then--and then when you've bled out
流血而死时  这就是你的下场
in some fucking shithole like this, and you will,
他们甚至不会参加你的葬礼
and they don't bother turning up for your funeral,
如果你有家人的话  他们会给你家
they'll just post your family, if you've got one,
邮递一枚勋章
a fucking medal.
就一枚勋章
A fucking medal!
还是二等的
Second class.
他们没回来救你  对吧
They never came back for you, did they?
都是因为这个  不是吗
That's what all this is about, isn't it?
好吧  我懂了
Yeah, I understand.
但你还是不会眼睁睁看我杀了你男朋友
But you're still not gonna let me kill your boy here.
-詹姆士  -不要
- James. - Don't--
不要哭的像个娘们
Don't whine like a girl.
-求你了  -有点男人样
- Please. - Be a man.
你做决定吧
Make a choice!
闭嘴
Shut the fuck up!
你最好能说服他
You'd better fucking convince him.
詹姆士  看着我  不要
James, look at me. Don't.
闭嘴
Shut the fuck up!
-詹姆士  求你了  -做决定吧
- James, please.  - Make a choice.
求你  别他们这么做  詹姆士
Please, don't let them do this. James. James!
别让他们这么做
Don't let them do this!
詹姆士  看着我  求你了
James. James, look at me, please!
七
7.
七号
7...
伊维尔路七号
Rue Eville.
干得好
Good work.
总部  收到了吗
Zero, did you copy that?
伊维尔路七号  伊维尔路七号
7 Rue Eville. 7 Rue Eville.
继续走  走啊
Go on. Move.
你这狗日的叛徒
You fucking traitor.
妈的
Fuck.
好了  跟我走  我们走
It's OK. Come with me. Let's go.
我们地狱见  士兵
I'll see you in hell, soldier.
这是什么东西
What the fuck you got there?
-阿迈  -是什么
- Mikey. - What the fuck is that?
总部这是  B2
Zero, this is Bravo Two.
"勇敢的心"和他男友已阵亡
Braveheart and his boyfriend KIA.
我们准备撤退
We're headed back to you now.
你收到地址了吗  伊维尔路七号
Did you copy that address, 7 Rue Eville?
收到  已经在路上了
Roger. On the road now.
报告你们集合点  我们去接你们  完毕
Radio your exfil, and we'll pick you up en route. Out.
你做到了
You've done it.
他就在这 瑞秋
He's here, Rachel.
我是道尔顿
Dalton.
收到  瑞秋你在哪
I copy. Where are you, Rachel?
我们在伊维尔路上
We're at Rue Eville.
坐在车上  静观其变
Sit tight and observe only.
保持通讯  我们在路上了
Stay on open channel. We're on our way.
道尔顿在伊维尔路  我们走
Dalton's at Rue Eville. Let's move!
上
Move!
把这姑娘带回天帐
Get the girl back to the Crib.
上车  快上车
Get in the car. Get in the car.
迈克尔  斯科特  你们和我一起
Mike, Scott, you're with me!
行动  行动  行动
Go, go. Go, go, go!
索菲亚
Sofia.
怎么现在才到
You've come a long way.
我丈夫在哪
Where's my husband?
他来不了了
He couldn't be here,
但是他让我转告你
but he told me to tell you
他真的很抱歉
he's truly sorry.
里面有枪声
I have a shot inside.
瑞秋  快离开那个房子
Rachel, get out of that house now.
离开那个房子  瑞秋
Get out of that house now, Rachel.
太迟了
Too late.
该死
Shit.
妈的
God damm it!
抱歉
Sorry.
你认识我  对吗
You know my face, do you?
机密档案上有我  对吧
From all those Special Branch files, right?
你算什么  士兵吗
What are you, a soldier?
英国妞  这一枪是为了我哥哥
Well, Brit, this one's for my brother.
妈的  你听到了吗
Fuck, did you hear that?!
麦坎娜
MacKenna.
所以  结局会是
So here's how it ends.
我出名
I'm famous,
你完蛋
and you're done.
妈的
Fuck.
该死
Shit.
向右
Going right.
她跑了
She's gone.
我来晚了
I was too late.
她从墙后跑的
Behind that wall!
不管索菲亚带着什么  她都拿走了
Whatever Sofia was carrying, she took it.
谁
Who?
马芮·麦坎娜  真爱尔兰共和军
Mairead MacKenna. Real IRA.
什么
What?
真爱尔兰共和军是怎么搅合进来的
What the fuck is the real IRA doing in the middle of this?
我不知道  但无线电里是她的声音
I don't know, but that was her voice on comms.
她说的没错
She was right.
妈妈我爱你
感谢上帝  你没事吧
Thank God you're all right!
我没事  你还好吗
I'm fine. Are you OK?
没事
Yeah.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你  爸爸
I love you, too, Dad.
我们得走了
We're gonna go.
等等
Wait. Um,
你也会是个好父亲的
you'd, um, make an all right dad, too.
真的吗
Really?
真是个好孩子
You're a pretty good kid.
我们走了
We're done.
一切都好
It's all good.
这是什么  鹅卵石吗
What is this? A pebble?
去你的  这才不是鹅卵石
Oh, fuck, it's not a pebble.
这可是非常值钱的鹅卵石
That would be one very expensive pebble.
是未切割的钻石
That is an uncut diamond.
真的吗
Really?
真的
Really.
值多少
How much?
足够你回家
It's enough for you to get home,
远离一切麻烦
get out of trouble.
为什么给我这个
Why are you doing this for me?
我不知道
I don't know.
也许是因为你想回家
Probably because you want to get home
看望家人
and see your family...
重修就好
fix things.
我要怎么谢你呢
And if I want to say "Thank you"?
要谢的话...
Well...
就从这开始
begin with this.
这可不是女孩的名字
That is not a girl's name.
是我住的酒店
It's my hotel.
你可别吃下去了
Don't eat that.
对你没好处
Not good for you.
他在哪儿
先给我钱
我只是在想  经历了这么多
I'm just thinking, what the fuck do we do
我们到底在做什么
after all this, you know?
你想金盆洗手吗
Are you talking about a get-out plan?
也许
Well, I suppose.
因为她  差点死在那儿了
Almost died out there because of her.
听着  不管她做事有多疯狂
Ah, look. No matter how crazy she was,
我都相信她这么做有正当的理由
I have to believe she did some things for the right reasons.
真的吗  比如害巴克斯特被爆头
Really, like getting Baxter killed?
不
No, no.
她倒是跟他落得同样下场
She did end up like him, though,
莱瑟比也是
and Leatherby.
或许他说的对
Maybe he was right.
谁
Huh?
莱瑟比  他说我们最终都会去同一个地方
Leatherby. We're all heading for the same place.
唯一不同的只是到达的时间
The only thing that changes is when we get there.
妈的  看来领退休金是不可能了
Fuck it. It's not like I got a great retirement, anyway.
别这样  这可说不准
Come on. I don't know about that.
混蛋
Shit.
你那份上交了吗
Did you hand yours in already?
看来没有
I'll take that as a no.
干得漂亮  斯顿布奇中士
Nice work, Sergeant Stonebridge.
如果我上交了  他们就可能会问
Yeah, well, if I did, they might start asking questions
"其余的钻石在哪儿"
like, were there any others?
有道理  原来你不交公是为了
Right, so you just didn't hand them in
保护我
to protect me.
当然要保护  你是我好兄弟
Yeah, I'm protecting you, my mate.
你这么说让我感觉好多了
Yeah. That makes me feel much better.
怎么
Uh-huh?
是
Yeah.
我们这就去
We're on it.
-该死  -他们说什么
- Shit. - What did they say?
他们在机场的监控录像上发现了麦坎娜
They spotted MacKenna on a CCTV camera at the airport.
她正要去布达佩斯
She's heading for Budapest.
这次算你们走运
朋友们